{
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "title": "week0",
        "questions": [
          {
            "index": 1,
            "question": "The ability to produce a good at a lower opportunity cost than another producer is a definition of",
            "options": ["Real advantage", "Monetary advantage", "Comparative advantage", "Opportunity advantage"],
            "correct": "Comparative advantage"
          },
          {
            "index": 2,
            "question": "Fluctuations in economic activity, such as employment and production, are referred to as",
            "options": ["Business cycles", "Economic cycles", "Production cycles", "Market cycles"],
            "correct": "Business cycles"
          },
          {
            "index": 3,
            "question": "The property of society getting the most it can from its scarce resources is a definition of",
            "options": ["Efficiency", "Equality", "Prudence", "Sustainability"],
            "correct": "Efficiency"
          },
          {
            "index": 4,
            "question": "In the word root for Economics, 'nemein' stands for",
            "options": ["Together", "To keep", "House", "Manage"],
            "correct": "Manage"
          },
          {
            "index": 5,
            "question": "Whatever must be given up to obtain some item is a definition of",
            "options": ["Explicit costs", "Implicit costs", "Opportunity costs", "Phantom costs"],
            "correct": "Opportunity costs"
          },
          {
            "index": 6,
            "question": "Rational decision making compares",
            "options": ["Average benefits to average costs", "Average benefits to marginal costs", "Marginal benefits to average costs", "Marginal benefits to marginal costs"],
            "correct": "Marginal benefits to marginal costs"
          },
          {
            "index": 7,
            "question": "Something that induces a person to act is a definition of",
            "options": ["Enticement", "Attraction", "Incentive", "Occupation"],
            "correct": "Incentive"
          },
          {
            "index": 8,
            "question": "Input costs that require an outlay of money are",
            "options": ["Explicit costs", "Implicit costs", "Opportunity costs", "Phantom costs"],
            "correct": "Explicit costs"
          },
          {
            "index": 9,
            "question": "The property of distributing economic prosperity uniformly among the members of society is a definition of",
            "options": ["Efficiency", "Equality", "Prudence", "Sustainability"],
            "correct": "Equality"
          },
          {
            "index": 10,
            "question": "The ability of an individual to own and exercise control over scarce resources is known as",
            "options": ["Property rights", "Resource rights", "Individual rights", "Social rights"],
            "correct": "Property rights"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
  